IGOR PAPRZYCKI

JAVA DEVELOPER



PHONE

+48 504 781 817

EMAIL

igypap@gmail.com

GITHUB

github.com/igorpaprzycki

WEB

igorpaprzycki.github.io

SUMMARY

Ambitious, highly skilled professional with over two years of experience in software development. Possess strong software skills in JAVA technologies. Have analytical and problem-solving skills combined with passion and commitment to software engineering. In the past worked for four years in aviation industry as process automation engineer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Technologies:	Tools:
- JAVA 8	- Jenkins
- Spring, SpringBoot	- Tomcat
- Hibernate, DB2, SQLite, MySQL,	- JIRA, Bitbucket, Bamboo, Confluence
SQLServer	- Platforms: Linux, Windows, Docker
- JUnit, Groovy, EasyMock, Mockito,	

DEV Tools:

Spock

- IntelliJ IDEA
- GIT, SVN
- Maven, gradle

Basic knowledge:

- HTML 5, CSS, JavaScript
- ReactJS
- Angular 6, TypeScript
- Karma, Jasmine

OTHER SKILLS

Business knowledge:

- Derivative market
- Clearing
- Trade processing
- Claim submission/processing

Other skills:

- Agile, scrum
- Fluent working english
- Teamworking, international environment

EXPERIENCE

Pragmasoft Sp. Z o. o. MAY 2018 - present

JAVA Developer

JAVA Developer in software house, working for external client in insurance industry. Developing web based application for claim submission in microservices architecture. As a teammate of scrum team responsible for software development, in full scrum lifecycle (backlog grooming, planning, sprints, retrospective).

Technology stack:

- Backend: JAVA 8, Spring, Hibernate, Soap, REST, Maven, GIT
- Frontend: Angular 6, TypeScript
- Test-driven development: JUnit, Groovy, Spock, Karma, Jasmine
- Databases: PostgreSQL
- Platforms: Docker, Windows (development)
- Atlassian Suite: Bitbucket, JIRA, Conuence, Bamboo
- Agile/Scrum: two-week sprintsp

IGOR PAPRZYCKI

JAVA DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE cont.

Goldman Sachs JUNE 2017 - APRIL 2018

Analyst JAVA Developer

JAVA Developer in Investment Banking industry responsible for software development, deployment and testing, providing high quality code and on-time delivery.

Working on Clearing House communication API implementation for internal trade and clearing processing.

Technology stack:

- JAVA 8, Spring, Maven, Gradle, JMS, SVN, Jenkins, Tomcat
- Test-driven development: JUnit, Groovy, EasyMock
- Databases: DB2
- Platforms: Linux (production), Windows (development)
- Project Management Tools: Atlassian Suite (JIRA, Confluence)
- Teamworking across dierent timezones

Freelancer APRIL 2016 - OCTOBER 2016

C++/QT Developer

The project deliverable was to develop GUI application providing MODBUS communication with industrial PLC controller & Ethernet IDS camera.

Application main tasks: calibration parameters settings, data acquisition, image capture, data analysis & report generation.

Technologies used: Qt Framework, MODBUS TCP/IP, multithreading, OpenCV library, STL containers.

Institute of Aviation JANUARY 2013 - MAY 2017

ENGINEER

Aviation engines Fan Blade Out facility design and commissioning. The Warsaw Institute of Aviation center can now boast of having the world's largest vacuum chamber. Designed for Fan Blade detachment tests in largest turbine engines. It is 12 meters long, it has 5.5 meters in internal diameter and weighs 177 tons.

My responsibilities: Data Acquisition, sensor instrumentation & HMI systems design and commissioning. Works mainly with National Instruments hardware and LabVIEW software.

EDUCATION

JAVA Bootcamp OCTOBER 2016 - MARCH 2017

akademiakodu.pl

Java BootCamp programming course for Android and Spring web application development.

Kielce University of Technology 2011 - 2012

MASTER OF SCIENCE (M. Sc.), Electrical Engineering

Graduation in 5% of the best University students.

Kielce University of Technology 2007 -2011

FIRST DEGREE ENGINEER, Electrical Engineering